my-free-mp3s.com 2005-05-05

# MyFreeMP3s.com | Privacy Policy

MyFreeMP3s.com's Privacy Policy:

MyFreeMP3s.com respects privacy of Internet Users and does not collect personally identifying information without the Internet User's permission. If you are a member of MyFreeMP3s.com, you can contact us regarding this privacy policy by logging into your account at www.MyFreeMP3s.com and going to our "Support" section. 

Collection of Data

MyFreeMP3s.com does not collect Internet User identity or contact information from Internet Users' visits to MyFreeMP3s.com websites. For each visitor to a MyFreeMP3s.com website, the visitor's computer reaches us via a particular IP (Internet Protocol) address. MyFreeMP3s.com's servers automatically collect this IP address. 

No information is obtained from the Internet User or Internet User's computer to generate the unique identifying number of the Internet User. MyFreeMP3s.com's servers automatically generate the unique number. None of MyFreeMP3s.com's cookies are used to perform "user profiling." 

MyFreeMP3s.com does receive and record partial e-mail addresses of Internet Users, only in circumstances where the Internet User has voluntarily provided its identity and contact information through the Advertiser's website. This partial e-mail address does not enable MyFreeMP3s.com to personally identify an Internet User. 

Use and Disclosure of Data

MyFreeMP3s.com does not sell or rent personally identifying information. MyFreeMP3s.com does not disclose personally identifying information to anyone that MyFreeMP3s.com is not authorized to do so. 

MyFreeMP3s.com reserves the right to release information on Internet Users if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. Disclosure shall be limited to only to those that MyFreeMP3s.com is compelled to disclose to. At present, all information processing occurs in the United States. 

Security Measures

MyFreeMP3s.com employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Access to MyFreeMP3s.com customer data is accessible via password protection through the Advertiser Account created by the Advertiser, and to designated MyFreeMP3s.com employees who require system level access in order to perform their jobs. Access to Internet User data that identifies the Internet User's name and/or e-mail addresses is limited to designated MyFreeMP3s.com employees who require such access in order to perform their jobs and to the Advertiser that provided such information. Each Advertiser is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of its own password used for accessing its accounts on the MyFreeMP3s.com Network. 

COPPA

Since you may not become a member of MyFreeMP3s.com's network if you are under the age of 18, MyFreeMP3s.com complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Advertisers and Publishers are also obligated to comply with COPPA. 

If you inform MyFreeMP3s.com that MyFreeMP3s.com has collected or received information from a child under 18, MyFreeMP3s.com will delete such information immediately from its databases. No MyFreeMP3s.com Web Site is specifically directed to children under 18. MyFreeMP3s.com shall not knowingly distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information erroneously collected from children under 18. 

Deactivating or deleting from databases by Publishers and Advertisers

Please contact us if you no longer wish to maintain an account with MyFreeMP3s.com, or are unable to access your account. If MyFreeMP3s.com has such information, MyFreeMP3s.com shall not retain your name and/or e-mail address any longer than is necessary to perform the services that you requested from MyFreeMP3s.com. To contact MyFreeMP3s.com, log in to your account at www.MyFreeMP3s.com and go to the "Support" section. 

Policy Changes

MyFreeMP3s.com may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by MyFreeMP3s.com prior to the effective date of the policy change. 

_Effective October 11, 2004_
